March 19.
On this day, a special event was held by renting out a movie theater
Yes, so, can you hear me, everyone?
Good afternoon, ladies and gentlemen.
Good afternoon.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for coming to the screening of Super Express The Movie.
ATTO HATSEN: Are you ready for the balloon?
New album released on March 22
B9
Meinari Okan
Included in its first limited edition Blu-ray
All the members of Super Tokkyu in their own words
the year 2022 in their own words.
Chotokukyu 2022 THE MOVIE
Ahead of the album release
A preliminary screening of the movie was held
We have to watch it too.
I'm so happy to be able to watch it with you all at the same time.
I'm so happy. I'm so happy.
It was a really fresh feeling.
This time, I'd like to show you a part of the event and
and a part of the video specially for you!
Hahahahaha!
I was the most nervous at the beginning.
It was amazing.
No doubt about it.
Really.
You're standing up.
You forgot to eat food for a few days in a row.
Yeah, I did.
At first.
You said...
I don't know.
I really did forget.
Your real face.
I was going to go with it.
I really almost fucked up.
Well, there's one person in the group I almost fucked up.
Who?
Me.
Who is it?
It's me.
It's you.
Mr. Yamada! Mr. Yamada! Yamada san! Yamada san!
Yamada san! Yamada san! Yamada san!
At the time, I felt really bad about it. I wanted to apologize.
It's not that Takashi's singing was lacking and I wanted to include it
Takashi couldn't sing the song he wanted to sing, so he had to be pulled out, right?
It was painful for me to see that.
But until now... we've been connected.
It's no exaggeration to say that Takashi is the one who's kept us together.
It's been a long few years since the six of us became five.
If you weren't around then, you wouldn't be here now.
Well, to put it another way, I still think of Takashi as the star of Chotokukyu.
Shu-Yan plays the leading role, but I still think of myself as Takashi.
I think that should be respected the most.
I understand. You get a lot of emotion and laughter.
I know.Yeah. - Yeah.
It was really like a live performance.
I'm sure, I'm sure, I'm sure.
It was like a live performance.
I saw a side of him that I didn't know existed.
I saw a side of Gido that I didn't know existed.
I mean, the feelings of the five of them.
I got to know what they were talking about at the audition.
I got to know more about them.
I was more moved than before.
And I...
I like them more.
What? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I like you five more now.
Oh!
That's what you said, Fukazawa.
I'm really going to hug you after that.
I'm going to hug you.
Chotoku Kyu 2022 THE MOVIE is
included in the limited first edition of the new album B9!
Please watch it!
And
B9 first limited edition B-1 performance
B9 release event held recently at La La Fort Tres
We wanted 4 new members to produce
New members produced the live show for the first time
What is the road to Toyosu, the sacred place after 8 years
Documentary closely followed by Super Tokkyu
Best 9
On this day, the members of Super Express were holding a live event at Tachicar
On this day, they held a live event at Tachicar
On this day, the members of Super Express were holding a live event at Tachikar
Cutting through the wind Our story
Let me take you to the ideal world
I'll draw it for you tomorrow, and it will echo in your heart
Spreading in your mind like a melting pot
You are all I want
Let me hear your heart
Looking forward
A few hours before this concert, four new members were suddenly summoned.
Good morning
Good morning, please.
Excuse me.
Please.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
After six months together.
Takashi has something to say.
I really think both of you guys have done a great job, and...
And, well...
2023, the three years we're going to be running...
I think I'd like to take a break.
I can't. I can't. I can't.
I'll just...
I have to hold on.
I have to grab it.
I was buzzing.
Oh, well...
And here we go to the point
You know... there's the Relieve...
On Toyosu.
I'm talking about that place.
Four new members...
What's the set list?
What kind of performance we're going to do.
How to present them.
For example, from the entrance
From the entrance to the exit
from the entrance to the exit
Produce
I just wanted to let you know
I wanted you to know that
The release event of the new album D9 will be held in Toyosu, and we would like to entrust the production of the event to a new member.The release event of the new album D9 to be held in Toyosu.
Here's what he had in mind
Toyosu is a sacred place for Chotek, and we've done a lot of free live shows there.
What we did back then...
We want people to experience what we did back then, as part of the 2 year development period that we've been in for over 10 years.
I think the Kusumi period is very important, and I don't think we've ever done that, so I'd like us to experience it as part of the 2-year development period that we've been doing for over 10 years.
I think it's important to have the Kusumi period, but I don't think we've done it yet.
I'd be happy if you could do some kind of project for us.
Yes, it's great!
Garigari fishing, garigari fishing, garigari fishing
Garigari Garigari
Garigari Garigari Garigari Garigari Garigari
This is a very important place for us, a sacred place for Super Express, where we have held many events since our debut.
We worked on an hourly wage, so we wrote the panels ourselves.
We were told to prepare these things, so we did everything ourselves.
We'd make up our own numbers, and we'd do the gymnastics.
Do you remember going to the store to buy aloe vera for the members?
It's funny, but I was the one who was asked to do it, not the manager.
I thought it was the most comfortable thing I'd ever done.
Why are you doing it?
Because I already had it, and it would be nice to have that kind of experience.
The new member who was entrusted with producing such an important event...
I'm really looking forward to it.
We've already talked about it.
I'm really excited about it.
We're going to set aside some time to have a meeting.
I've always wanted to experience this.
So I'm pretty excited.
I've been thinking a lot about how I want to perform live.
I've been thinking about it.
So I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm sure it's going to be great.
I'm hoping to give a performance that will move the audience.
I think it would be great if I could give a performance that would move the audience.
I'd like to take that as a chance and do my best.
I really made everything myself.
We didn't have anything to do with the manager or anything like that.
I think it's amazing that we did it all by ourselves.
I think it's amazing.
I wanted to do my best, too.
And the next day, right after that...
It's been a long time!
It's been a long time since I've felt like a topping mall.
This is Snick.
I don't think I've ever been on this side.
Look at this side.
Oh, is that down here?
What's going on here?
We'll use this stage for the release event.
What do you think? Look at this.
I can almost swing.
Can we get on the stage?
Jerry, would you stand right there for a second?
It's huge.
Oh, man.
You can barely see back there.
And then, right away...
They're going to throw balloons at us from up there.
Balloons?
It's funny, they're just falling.
Oh, from over here?
From up there.
For example, there is a space for two people to walk on this dirt line,
Then, they can walk up the straight line on the lawn and climb up.
Oh, I think we can do that. Oh, can we do that?
If you tell them in advance.
I don't know, don't you want to be particular about the background?
Even if it's just that width.
Just here?
Just the width of the stage?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Isn't it totally different?
We should buy the mastermind and do it ourselves.
If we're going to go to all this trouble, let's do it right. It'll double the video.
We can do a lot of things!
Ideas came out one after another as they saw the venue for the actual event.
The new members were filled with anticipation.
Six days later
It's started. Let's do it!It's started. Let's do it.
Where do we start?
We talked about the live plan remotely, taking time out of our schedules.
Well, let's just say what songs we want to play.
By the way, we should probably decide how many songs we want to play and how many songs we want to play.
That's a 30-minute slot.
I'll do four, five songs.
That's about 5 songs!
Okay, Haru, tell us all the songs you've got.
Let's see, BURN.
Train, DDD.
The rest are up to you.
What about you, Masa?
I think I'll start with New World.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Train, DDD, and Moran Moran.
And finally, BURN or My Buddy.
You've gone all cool and stylish.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Yes, we did.
Each of you raised your high stations to decide the set list.
What to do with Run or DDD?
This is a tough one.
But I'm thinking Run, because it's so easy to understand.
I'll be so scared if I put it in later, when I'm sure that BURN will be the end of the game for all of us!
I'll do that. I thought running was good too.
Running is fun.
One more song, right?
Yeah. - Yeah.
If you had to choose between MY BUDDY and BURN, which would you choose? Hey, guys.
I'd say BURN.
If I had to choose.
If you're talking about getting people involved...
BURN is the way to go.
Even if people don't know the song, they can get on board.
That's possible.
You can get people's attention, right?
Yes, that's right.
BURN can get you out.
Yeah, I think I can play it, so I'll say Burn.
So, why don't we just call it Burn?
All right, all full.
That's good, that's good, that's good.
That's great.
We're going to wear them all.
And I'm particularly particular about one of the songs.
The way you put the MC...
Yeah.
I don't think one is enough.
You definitely want to put it in before the "Mola Mola".
Yeah, I'd love to put that in there.
MORA MORA, the lead song from Chotokukyu's new album
MORA MORA, the lead song from B9, will be performed for the first time at this event.
I won't talk about what kind of song it is in front of MORA MORA, but I want to make sure we can take videos here.
MORA MORA? After the performance, I said, "Please use TikTok and other social networking sites to share the video.
Okay, now,
I think we've got the song set.
I think we have a set of songs.
That's it.
That's right.
We'll go over the details of the stage direction.
The way we're going out.
We wanted something elaborate.
The entrance was a little elaborate.
The one I was talking about... the bar that we're going to put on from inside the building, like an SP, and everyone will be super surprised.
Then everyone will come in, and what if they don't know about the surprise?
But I can do that.
And then they'll walk in and appear right there in the middle of the stage.
I think it'd be really, really funny.
I think it's good, too. I think we'll take a break now.
Okay, good night!
The new members took a break from the location shoot to report back to the older members about what they had worked out.
We came up with the B9 release event.
We'll start with the order of the songs, five in all.
The first song is Retrain.
Retrain
The reason why we chose Retrain was because it was the first single!
It's not like going back to the beginning.
So I put Retrain as the first song.
The second song is New World.Second song New World.
The coolest song I can do right now.
I'll show you coolness in these two songs first.
Then MC on 3
Third song, Moramora.
I decided to make all of Moramora OK for filming.
I'm going to have them film it.
I'm going to have that person send out a message.
And after that, we'll have a little bit of MC.
After that, we'll have a little bit of MC, and then we'll start the show with "Burn".
The reason why I chose "Running Super Express" at the end is...
Real talk, it's a little bit different from the previous super express.
I'm not saying it's a change from the past, but we're going back to the basics to show you how cool we are.
I think there might be a few fans who might be a little confused, so I decided to make a new start
I wanted to tell the fans that we are going to run together.
I wanted to convey this message to the fans.
The week when the setlist was announced along with his thoughts on the songs he chose
He also explained the production plan in detail.
I dared to put on a speed-platform around the shopping mall.
We had all the staff members wear T-shirts that said "Super Surprise" on them.
We would walk to the stage and perform while selling our name.
I'm sure there will be a lot of people wondering who those people are.
I'm sure there will be a wide variety of people.
Another thing...
I'm going to drive out.
Car arrives.
I'm coming out.
I'm walking in all dressed up.
And I'm going into the venue.
I don't think the people who are coming to the show
They don't really know what's going on.
And if you go to YouTube, you can see all of that.
I have to make it so that people can see the whole thing if they go to YouTube.
Hmmm...
I was like, "Hmmm.
And when the opening essay is playing.
I'm going to drop bird feathers from above.
I'm going to do a fantastic spray of that mola-mola costume.
If I just did cool stuff.
Because there are so many cool things in the world
there are so many cool things in the world.
That's why we have to change the way we appear on stage.
I think that if I don't change the way I appear and create a buzz
Yes, sir.
What do you think?
I think it's good.
Well, I have my own feelings about it, and I don't mind if it's just one thing.
But Yuki, who usually directs live shows... has one thing on his mind.
What everyone said was that many of the items looked good in a box.
I think it's a good idea.
There were too many things that looked good in a box.
Of course, I think they were talking about the meaning of doing a free live show, but...
But for me, the most important thing is to win and make the fans happy.
I think that's the most important thing.
For example, you used a lot of LEDs even though it was a free concert.
I think that's really great.
I think it's something like that.
I think it's something like that, but the level of the ideas that everyone is coming up with is pretty high.
I don't think we could have come up with something like that if we had been doing free shows back then.
So to be honest, when I hear that
I think it would be cooler if we could do it in a box with proper lighting or something.
Organic and Takuya pointed out the sense of hope in the direction.
This live concert is not held in a large venue with a set and lighting, but on a special outdoor stage.
I don't think that's what a free concert is about.
In the world, that's what I'm thinking.
If I think that's what the audience wants, I don't think that's what they want.
I understand, and it's because I have all the feelings and enthusiasm.
I think there's a lot of things that are probably expanding.
I'll give you more advice, choosing my words carefully.
Furthermore, if you consider it as a free live performance, then...
If you consider it as a free concert, you don't have to play cute and fun songs anymore.
So I thought it might be okay to go with a cool event.
The theme of the new album is
Cool & Stylish, and the important point is how much we can show it in the short time we have for the live performance.
Thank you very much.
Free live shows are very close to the audience.
First of all, we should not forget about the people who are there.
I think it's important to leave your mark on the environment you're in.I think it's a question of how much of a mark you can leave on the environment you've been blessed with.
I think that's the first step.
I thought so.
It's hard, isn't it?
It's all I can say.
I'm sorry.
It's a new start.
I hope we can take a good step forward tomorrow.
I can feel that they've given it a lot of thought.
I hope it was a good experience for them.
We want to show them what we want to show them.